[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 8, "question": "Did the president call?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 9, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "NN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 43, "question": "What do they need from somebody like you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 44, "answer": "Well, they all have something different.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 48, "question": "When that specific thing is happening, what do you say?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 49, "answer": "It's not a say, it's putting him back in state.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "RB", "VB", ",", "RB", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 69, "question": "I mean despite all these incredible things that you've experienced, to have the president of your country call you in his great hour of need?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 70, "answer": "Well, you know, if you're thinking about yourself in a moment like that, you can't really serve, so then it would be all about you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 84, "question": "Do you personally ever have crushing moments of self-doubt?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "VBP", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 85, "answer": "Self-doubt as often as you do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 97, "question": "Now be honest, when you first heard that, what was your reaction?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VB", "VBN", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 98, "answer": "That was pretty horrific.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "IN", "NN", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "NNS", "VBG", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 118, "question": "How helpful is that to exuding the kinds of inner self-belief that you clearly have?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "IN", "TO", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 119, "answer": "Well, clearly it's not just about inner self-belief, it's really about people getting to the truth.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 146, "question": "Did she ever tell you she loved you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 147, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 159, "question": "OK?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "aSentId": 160, "answer": "Sounds like perfect.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 239, "question": "What does he need?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 240, "answer": "I'm a strategist.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 260, "question": "In one minute or two?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "CD", "NN", "CC", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 261, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 299, "question": "What's the last one of your five points?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "IN", "PRP$", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 300, "answer": "It's the health side.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBG", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 341, "question": "How are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 342, "answer": "I love the way you were laughing so uncomfortably at yourself dancing there.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 343, "question": "Well, I mean, could you imagine if you were dancing like that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 344, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 347, "question": "Oh, it is?", "question_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 348, "answer": "Pretty much, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 356, "question": "Do you still look on scenes like that with great affection or does it become this terrible curse you wish you'd ever been involved with?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 357, "answer": "Hardly.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 364, "question": "\"Seinfeld\"?", "question_pos_tagged": ["``", "NNP", "''", "."], "aSentId": 365, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "RP", "TO", "WRB", "JJ", ":", "RB", "TO", "WRB", "JJ", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 367, "question": "At moment when you first start making (INAUDIBLE), at what moment do you start thinking -- actually this could be huge?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "WP", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", ":", "RB", "DT", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 368, "answer": "I think I never really caught up to how big -- honestly to how big it was until right before we ended.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 369, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 370, "answer": "I swear to you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 381, "question": "Didn't like 100 million people watch that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "VB", "CD", "CD", "NNS", "JJ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 382, "answer": "I don't remember.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 385, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 386, "answer": "It was like a Super Bowl, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 389, "question": "Do we have a fact checker here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 390, "answer": "If I'm exaggerating, go with me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 403, "question": "Do you have like little \"Seinfeld\" reunions in some dingy little bar in Manhattan?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "``", "NNP", "''", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 404, "answer": "We get together on a daily basis.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Manhattan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 408, "question": "Do the ships just pass out of the port and that's it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 409, "answer": "We do see each other on occasion.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 423, "question": "What is it about that show, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 424, "answer": "Well, I think it's a couple things.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "TO", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 515, "question": "Don't you have a bleeper here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 516, "answer": "Yes, we're going to have to now.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJR", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 531, "question": "Did you have more or less sympathy for her by the end of your process, just on what it takes to be a vice president?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJR", "CC", "JJR", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "RB", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 532, "answer": "I have more sympathy for all women in government.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sarah Palins"]}, "docId": "120505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "RBR", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 535, "question": "More Sarah Palins?", "question_pos_tagged": ["JJR", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 536, "answer": "No, not more Sarah Palins in my opinion.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sarah Palins"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", ":", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", ":"], "qSentId": 548, "question": "No, I mean just generally for women in America right now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 549, "answer": "Well, it's interesting because all of these issues are -- trans-vaginal probes and --", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 579, "question": "Are you expecting some sharp flip-flopping?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 580, "answer": "I know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 584, "question": "What do you make of your country right now generally?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 585, "answer": "I love it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 593, "question": "What is the solution for America?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 594, "answer": "I have no idea.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 600, "question": "How are we going to get there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 601, "answer": "For my children, I want my children to be active.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 606, "question": "What else?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 607, "answer": "That's good.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 615, "question": "You do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 616, "answer": "Yes, it's why you should be running for office.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 622, "question": "What office do you think I should run for?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 623, "answer": "I would go on the anti-transvaginal probe brigade.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 652, "question": "What part of that character did he fall in love with?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 653, "answer": "I'm not sure any part of it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 656, "question": "Yeah, you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 657, "answer": "Yes, definitely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VB", "POS", "NN", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 674, "question": "How have the pair of you, who are in the same profession, managed to stay happily married for 25 years?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 675, "answer": "Well, let's see, first of all, we're separating.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 680, "question": "How did you know he was the right guy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 681, "answer": "Here's the deal.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 694, "question": "Do you feel lucky?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 695, "answer": "I do feel lucky.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 702, "question": "Do you make each other laugh?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 703, "answer": "Oh, yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "``", "NNP", "''", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 706, "question": "Because there's an \"SNL\" battle every day?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "``", "NNP", "''", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 707, "answer": "No, it's not an \"SNL\" battle.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 715, "question": "Are you seriously about to split up?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "TO", "VB", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 716, "answer": "No, I'm kidding.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 730, "question": "What could go wrong?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 731, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]